Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com
한글자막제작 by 홍자막
hongej89@naver.com
내 말은, 모든 사람들은
자기가 영웅이 되길 바란다고
I mean, everyone wants to believe
they'd be the hero,
that they'd join the Resistance,
try to kill Hitler.
레지스탕스에 가입한다든지
히틀러를 죽이려고 한다든지
It's such fucking bullshit.
그런짓은 정말 멍청한거야
It's obedience, not resistance.
복종이 중요해,
저항이 아니라
That's the glue of every country,
every army, every religion in the world.
복종이 이 세계의 모든 국가, 군대,
종교의 접합체 역할을 한다고
The fuck are you talking about, Felix?
뭔 개소리하는거야, 펠릭스
What do you think?
I'm talking about us.
뭔 소리 같냐?
지금 우리 이야길 하는거라고
- I'm talking about our revolution.
- We snatched some rocks.
- 우리의 혁명을 말하는거야
- 우린 그냥 돌맹이 몇개 훔친건데
Mark my words, Wolfie,
this score is going to change our lives.
내 말을 명심해, 울피(볼프강 애칭)
이번 건이 우리의 인생을 바꿀거야
Not gonna change shit
if we can't sell them.
이거 못팔면
아무것도 안바뀌어
He's going to buy.
이 사람은 살거야
Just relax. Let me do the talking.
긴장하지말고,
대화는 내가 할게
- Thank you for waiting.
- Not a problem.
- 기다려주셔서 감사합니다
- 별 말씀을요
It's nice here, but you know
there's a bigger one in Mettre?
장소가 좋네요,
근데 Mettre에 더 큰게 있지않나요?
That one smells like piss.
거긴 지린내가 나요
The drunks from the park
use it as a toilet.
공원의 취객들이
화장실로 쓴답니다.
I like this one better.
전 여기가 더 좋아요
Whenever I have a difficult
decision to make, I come here.
언제든 어려운 결정을 내릴때면,
전 여기로 옵니다.
This place brings a clarity
to any decision.
이 장소는 어떤 결정이든
명확하게 내리는걸 도와주거든요
- What were you thinking about?
- My mother.
- 무슨 생각을 하고 계셨나요?
- 제 어머니요
- Did she die in the Holocaust?
- No, she lived.
- 유대인 대학살때 돌아가셨나요?
- 아뇨, 그땐 생존하셨어요
She fell in love with an Englishman
and ran away with him
영국남자와 사랑에 빠져서,
멀리 도망갔었죠
against her parents' wishes.
부모님의 바람도 져버리고요
I think how much courage she had
to make that decision.
그 결정을 내릴때 얼마나
큰 용기를 내셨을지 생각했습니다
After the war, she came back
to find her parents, but she never did.
전쟁 이후에, 돌아와서 부모님을
찾아다녔지만 결국 못찾았죠
- And she never left Berlin again.
- Mm.
그후론 다시는 베를린을
떠나지 않으셨습니다
Our existence depends
on sheer implausibility,
우리의 존재는 완전히
믿기 힘든것에 달려있죠
which I'm sure is exactly
how your merchandise
제가 보기엔 확실히
당신의 물품도
found its way into your pocket.
당신들 주머니에 들어가기까지
그랬을것 같네요.
Does that mean you're interested?
그 말뜻은 관심이
있다는건가요?
I would like to see them.
물품을 한번
보고 싶네요
Please, not here.
제발, 여기서 말고요
Any talk of money
seems unimportant here.
여기서 돈 이야기를 나누는것은
별로인것 같네요.
We never discuss money.
우린 돈 이야기를 하지않습니다
We have no interest in money.
저흰 돈에 관심이 없습니다.
All we are interested in
is making sure that you and your son...
저희의 모든 관심은
아버님과 아드님
- And your daughter.
- ...are happy.
- 그리고 따님이
- 행복하신거죠
OK, then we are all in accordance with--
그래요, 그럼 우린
모든 절차를 그대로...
Not exactly. Ah.
그건 아니구요, 아
We have spoken to the priest, uh,
저희가 사제와
이야기를 나눠보았습니다.
- concerning the, uh--
- Adjustment to the service.
- 그거에 관해서 이야기를...
- 식의 변화에 대해서요
Uh, this is my fault.
어, 이건 제 탓이에요
I wanted to add an exchange of rings.
저는 반지 교환식을
넣고 싶었거든요
Ah, this is a Hindu wedding ceremony.
There are no rings.
아, 이건 힌두식 결혼식입니다
반지는 없어요
- I know.
- There are traditions.
- 알아요
- 전통식으로 하는겁니다
Yes, but we are trying to start them
on a path to the 21st century,
알아요, 그런데 지금 21세기에
결혼시키는것 아닙니까?
- not the 16th.
- Of course.
- 16세기에 결혼시키는게 아니라
- 당연하죠
And the priest is ready to accommodate.
그리고 사제님들도
조정할 준비가 되있습니다.
It's just that with both services,
it appears the ceremony--
문제는 그 두가지 모두 하기엔
식이 조금 길게...
- Will be over six hours.
- Six hours?
- 6시간 넘게 될겁니다
- 6시간?
There are certain shortcuts
that others have preferred.
다른 고객분들이 선호하는
지름길 같은게 있습니다만
How short?
얼마나 짧게요?
It depends entirely on how much
you value the priest conducting it.
진행하는 사제분에게 성의를
보여주는만큼 달라지죠
How much?
그래서 얼마요?
The more you give him,
the shorter the ceremony.
돈을 더 내실수록
식은 더 짧아집니다
The sooner everyone can get to dancing.
그럼 모두가 더 빨리
춤추러 갈수있겠죠
Six hours is the starting point.
Pay him double, out in three.
6시간이 기점입니다
2배를 내시면 3시간이죠
And how much to not perform it at all?
그럼 아예 예식절차를
안하려면 얼마입니까?
You couldn't afford it.
감당 못하실겁니다
This is important to me.
이건 제게 중요해요
Married men in India don't wear rings.
인도남자들은 결혼해도
반지를 안껴요
There is nothing to show their commitment.
그들의 서약을 보여줄게
아무것도 없는거죠
That is why I want one.
그래서 전 반지를 원해요
I want to remember this night
for the rest of my life,
전 오늘밤을 제 평생동안
기억하고 싶어요
and I don't want it to be a secret.
그리고 비밀로
하고 싶지 않아요
I want the whole world to know
I'm bound to this woman.
온 세상에 제가 이 여자것인걸
알려주고 싶어요
Now and forever.
지금부터 영원히
I'm so proud of you.
너가 정말 자랑스럽구나
So smart and so strong.
아주 똑똑하고 아주 강하네
Is that why my father hates me?
그래서 아빠가
절 싫어하는거에요?
He doesn't hate you, my child.
아빠는 널 싫어하는게
아니란다, 애야
You must never think that.
절대 그렇게
생각하지마렴
- He loves you.
- He never came to any of my matches.
- 아빠는 널 사랑하셔
- 아빠는 제 시합에 한번도 안오셨어요
He went to all of Joong-Ki's matches.
중기의 시합엔 전부 가셨구요
You cannot be jealous of your brother.
동생을 질투하면 안돼
Do not blame him
for how much Father loves him.
아빠가 동생만 챙긴다고
동생을 미워하면 안된단다
It is natural for fathers
to be close to their sons.
아빠가 아들을 더
챙기는건 당연한 일이야
He's planning on Joong-Ki
taking over the company.
아빠는 중기에게 회사를
물려줄 계획이 있으시거든
If I cannot be there
to help Father realize his dream...
만약 엄마가 아빠의 꿈
이루는걸 못돕는다면...
you must be there for me.
너가 엄마대신
도와드리렴
Please, Sun, take care of your brother.
선아, 제발
동생을 잘챙겨주렴
Do this for me.
엄마를 위해서 그래줘
We, like these books,
or these diamonds,
우리들은, 이 책들이나
이 다이아처럼
have the secrets of our past
hidden inside us.
과거의 비밀을 우리
속에 숨겨두고 있지
You think a lot about the past, don't you?
과거를 많이
생각하시는군요, 그쵸?
Without the past,
there would be nothing to think about,
과거가 없다면,
생각할것이 없는거지
let alone someone to think it.
다른사람이 생각하는건
냅두게나
Deep.
심오하네요
You certainly weren't lying.
These are beauties.
확실히 거짓말을 한게 아니였군,
다이아가 아주 예뻐
Shall I be honest?
솔직하게 말해도 되겠나?
I know I was probably
the last on your list.
내가 당신들 구매자목록의
마지막 같은데
I'm an outsider to you, but I think I know
where these rocks came from.
내가 당신에겐 이방인이지만,
난 이 다이아의 출처를 알것 같소
Out of Mumbai, I'm guessing, and I know
who's going to come looking for them.
뭄바이 시내에서, 예상컨데 이걸
찾으러 다니는 사람도 알것같네
They will not be easy to move,
unless I recut them.
이것들은 옮기기 힘들걸세,
내가 재세공을 하지않는다면
Recut, they will have
a fraction of their worth.
재세공을 한다면
값어치가 떨어지지
Let's go, Felix.
I knew this was a waste of time.
가자, 펠릭스
시간 낭비일줄 알았어
Hang on. Really?
After we listened to all your bullshit?
기다려봐, 정말요? 당신이
하는 모든 잡소리를 다 들어줬는데?
If you were listening to my bullshit,
I said it would not be easy.
내 잡소리를 듣고있었다면,
내가 어려울꺼라했지
I didn't say it would not be possible.
안된다는 소리는
안했을텐데
I will buy a third of them
and see what I can do.
먼저 3분의 1을 사고
어떻게할지 결정하겠소
Half or nothing.
절반 아님 안팔아요
And we both know that you're going
to say yes, because I was listening.
그리고 이 제안을 받아들일걸 압니다
왜냐면 당신이 하는 소리를 들었으니
That's what your mother would do.
당신의 어머니라면
했을 일이잖아요
I'm such a bad person.
이 애미가 참 못났구나
You spend all your money on my medicine.
아들 돈을 전부
내 약으로 써버리니
- Don't talk like that.
- You would be a success without me.
-그렇게 이야기하지마세요
- 이 애미만 없었으면 너는 성공했을꺼다
- You would not have to live here.
- Not listening.
- 이런곳에서 살 필요도 없지
- 안들려요
If I wasn't such a bad person,
이 애미가 못나지만 않았다면
I'd stop taking my medicine
and let you get on with your life.
약 먹는것 그만두고
아들 인생 펼치도록 두는건데
This is my life.
This is why we came here.
이게 제 인생이에요
여기 온 이유가 있잖아요
To make money,
to be happy, to be healthy.
돈도 벌면서, 행복하게 지내고
건강하게 살려고요
Besides, when I iron my shirt,
it always burns up.
그리고 제가 직접 다리미질하면
맨날 옷 태워먹어요
Without you,
I would go into the world naked.
엄마 없이는,
전 옷벗고 다녀야돼요.
There's still some water left.
물이 조금 남아있네요
I will try and bring some back
before I come home.
집에 돌아올때
물 사오도록 할게요
I love you.
사랑해요 엄마
And don't worry.
그리고 걱정마요
I've got a feeling today
is going to be a really good day. Huh?
제 느낌으론 오늘은
아주 좋은날이 될것 같아요
Hey!
어이!
Ah!
아!
All aboard the Van Damn,
the safest bus in and out of Nai-robbery!
모두 밴 담에 승차하세요,
범죄로비에서 가장 안전한 버스입니다!
Eh?
엉?
The fuck are you doing?
뭐하고 서있어?
I'm thinking about Katrina Unger.
카트리나 우나
를 생각중이야
- What?
- Remember?
- 뭐라고?
- 기억안나?
The first time I got my dick wet.
내가 동정딱지
처음으로 땐 날
She was 16, I was 14.
걔는 16살이였고, 나는 14살
I'd been dating her for two months,
두 달간 사귀었는데
which back then
seemed like a fucking lifetime,
그 때는 무슨 평생처럼
긴 시간 같았지
and I remember thinking
I'd been wasting my time.
그땐 내가 시간낭비라고
생각했던게 기억이 나
Buying her presents,
taking her to the movies.
걔한테 선물 사다주고
영화 같이 보러가고
But then...
하지만 딱
the second I got myself
inside of her...
그 여자애 안에
박는 순간 느꼈지
everything...
everything had been worth it.
모든게...그 모든게
투자할 가치가 있었다고
Hm?
흠?
- Know what I did?
- What?
- 내가 뭐했는줄 알아?
- 뭘?
I went out and bought myself
a new pair of shoes.
밖에 나가서 내 자신한테
신발 한 켤래를 사줬지
Had to. I couldn't walk
in those old shoes anymore.
샀어야만 했어, 더 이상 오래된
신발을 신고 다닐 수 없었다고
From that point on, everything changed.
그 순간부터
모든게 변했어
I mean, I had changed. I was a man!
내 말은, 내가 변했지
남자가 된거야!
And right now, I'm thinking...
그리고 지금,
내가 생각하는건...
we need new shoes.
우린 새 신발이 필요해
Whoo!
워후!
This is it, Capheus!
바로 이거야,
카페우스
You'll never hear me complain
about success, Capheus, never!
앞으로 절대 내가 성공에 대해서
불평 안할게, 카페우스, 절대로!
- Never!
- My ancestors would haunt me
- 절대로!
- 내 조상님들도 나를 괴롭힐꺼야
if I even thought to complain
about having too many passengers.
승객들이 너무 많다고
불평하면 말야
- Whoo!
- Don't complain, Jela.
- 워후!!
- 불평하지마, 젤라
Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
*절대 따라하지마세요*
Whoo! Oh, those are my-- Those are
my ancestors reminding me to be grateful,
아, 저건 조상님들이 항상
감사하며 살라고 보낸거야
even when I'm being whipped on the face!
얼굴에 싸대기를 맞아도 말야
- Whoo!
- You are crazy.
너 미친놈 같아
Oh, my God!
오, 마이 갓!
Oh, my God.
오, 마이 갓..
Oh, crap.
오, 이런 똥같은
You made sure
we had all the permits, eh?
우리 확실히
허가 다 받은거 맞지?
Yeah, we are in total compliance.
Don't worry, it will be over in a minute.
그래, 우린 확실히 규정 준수했어.
걱정마, 1분도 안걸릴거야
Good day, officers.
I'm sure you'd like to see--
수고하십니다, 경관님
여기 확인하시려고...
- Shut the fuck up.
- Oh, happy to. Love to.
- 닥치고 짜져
- 오, 당연하죠, 닥칠게요
You know what? Shutting the fuck up
is a specialty of mine, so--
그거 알아요? 닥치고 짜지는게
제 특기인데, 그래서...
We want Van Damme.
반 담 어딨어
Out.
나와
Out, out, out, out.
나와 나와
튀어 나와
Shut up.
입 다물어
- Follow me.
- I don't understand, sir.
- 따라와
- 경관님, 왜 이러시죠
Follow me.
따라오라고
Guys, come on.
저기, 이러지마요
It seems he's not coming back.
이제 못 돌아올것 같은데?
Van Damme always comes back.
반 담은 항상 돌아와
Daniella, I don't think you both
were listening to me.
다니엘라, 너네 둘 다
내 말 안들었나본데
What I'm saying is that
he came to the set.
내 말은 그사람이
촬영장까지 왔다니까
- He came to the fucking set.
- The director says he knows him.
- 미친 촬영장까지 왔다고
- 감독이 그 사람 안다며
Yes, he did.
그래, 그랬지
And what did he say about him?
그래서 감독은
뭐라든?
He said he was a great guy.
감독은 그 사람이
좋은 사람이라던데
I'm sorry, Lito.
리토, 미안해
That doesn't sound like
something he would do.
근데 그 사람이
그럴 사람은 아닌데
Well, he did. He did.
근데 그랬다니까,
찾아왔다고
I'm telling you, Daniella, over lunch...
내말 들어봐,다닐라
점심 먹을때...
he showed me how to cut a man's throat.
그 인간이 사람 목 따는
법을 알려줬다니까
He put a knife on my throat.
내 목에 칼을
들이밀었다고
Now that sounds like
something he would do.
이제 그 사람이
할만한 짓 같네
- But now you're home, OK?
- You should have told me.
- 근데 넌 이제 집이잖아, 응?
- 말해 줬어야지
Taste the ceviche.
세비체(페루음식) 맛 좀 봐
Daniella-- Good.
다니엘라... 좋아
- You're an actor.
- Good?
- 넌 배우잖아
- 걍 좋네?
You understand that this,
you know, set, is--
너 이해하잖아 그,
배우한테 촬영장이란
- It's a sacred space?
- Yes, exactly.
- 성스러운 공간이다?
- 그래, 바로 그거야
- I thought home was your sacred space.
- It is, Hernando.
- 집이 성스러운 공간이라더니
- 맞아, 헤르난도
But this is where I work
and it's very difficult to concentrate
내 직장이잖아
집중하기가 힘들어지지
when you have a knife-wielding
psycho ex-lover stalking you.
칼들고 다니는 싸이코
전애인이 너를 스토킹하면
- You know, guys?
- Oh, my God.
- 뭔말인지 알지, 애들아?
- 오, 마이 갓.
Yeah, I mean,
it completely freaked me out.
그래, 내 말은,
완전히 소름끼쳤다고
Oh, my God, this is so good.
오, 마이 갓
이거 너무 맛있어
That's the best ceviche I've ever tasted.
내가 먹어본 세비체중에
제일 맛있어
Oy, Hernando,
you have to open a restaurant.
오이, 헤르난도
레스토랑 하나 차리자
Thank you.
고마워용
I mean, you are such a good cook.
내 말은, 넌 요리를 너무 잘해
- I'm gonna tell you my secret.
- It's very tasty.
- 내 비결 하나 알려줄까?
- 이거 정말 맛있다
Actually, this is not, uh, ceviche.
사실은, 이게 정확히
세비체는 아냐
This is actually a mix.
이건 사실 퓨전이야
So, here they are.
자, 여기 있습니다
Yeah, great.
네, 좋네요
- Um... and I really like those ones, 42.
- Mm-hm.
음..그리고
이것들이 좋네요, 42
Und, do you have them in yellow,
something more colorful?
이거 노란색이라던지,
좀더 발랄한 색으로?
- Yeah, for sure.
- Oh, great.
- 네, 알겠습니다
- 좋아요
Wow.
와우
Those are so you, Wolfie.
그건 정말
너 같다, 울피
Maybe too you. You should
try something... a little different.
어쩌면 너무 너 같다
좀 다른걸 신어봐
I like my shoes.
난 내 신발이
맘에 들어
What the fuck?
이게 뭐야?
What?
뭔데?
I have seen you before.
전에 봤던
기억이 나요
- You pray to Ganesha.
- I do.
- 가네샤한테 기도했었죠
- 네, 그랬어요
If these men are allowed
to have their way,
이 사람들을 그냥 냅두면
you will never be allowed to pray again.
당신은 두번 다시
기도 못하러와요
What?
뭐라고요?
They want to strip away our traditions.
이 사람들은 우리
전통을 없애버리려해요
They are trying to destroy our India
and turn it into America.
우리 인도를 부셔버리고
미국으로 바꿔버리려 한다고요
- No, that-- That's not true.
- It is.
- 아뇨, 그건 사실이 아니에요
- 사실이에요
These are the facts.
여기 증거들이 있어요
They use their evil drug money
to buy politicians,
그들은 유해한 약을 판
돈으로 정치인들을 매수했어요
who are going to outlaw people like us
and temples like this.
우리 같은 사람과 신전을
불법화 시키려는 정치인들을요
We are pledged to come here every day
and pray for their deaths.
그들의 죽음을 위해 매일 모여
기도하기로 맹세했습니다.
Pray with us.
기도에 참여하세요
Pray to Ganesha to destroy our enemy
before they destroy us.
가네샤에게 적이 우릴 치기전에
적을 부셔달라고 기도합시다
So this is the notorious Van Damme.
그래서 당신이
악명높은 반 담이군요
I'm Silas Kabaka.
전 사일러스 카바카입니다
I know who you are.
누군지 알아요
Our reputations precede us.
우리의 명성이 앞섰군요
You did me a great service,
though you may not even know it.
당신은 모르겠지만
저게 큰 공헌을 하셨습니다
You see, the gang Superpower
had been working for me.
슈퍼파월 갱단이 제 밑에서
일했던걸 아실겁니다
They got it in their heads
they no longer needed me,
그러다가 머리가 굵어지고
더 이상 제가 필요없다고 하더군요
and in one afternoon,
you destroyed whatever reputation
그리고 어느날 오후,
그들이 세웠다고 생각한 명성을
they felt they'd been building,
당신이 짓밟아버렸습니다.
thereby saving me from
the incumbent messiness of betrayal.
그래서 제 손으로 배신의
댓가를 안갚아도 됐죠
So I said to myself,
그래서 제가 속으로
here is a man that might be capable
of more service to someone like me.
나를 위해 일을 해줄
사람이 여기 있구나 했습니다.
Service that provides the kind of
remuneration that can change a man's life.
인생을 바꿀만한 큰 보수
주는 일을 말이죠
Thanks for the offer, but I'm OK.
제안은 고맙지만,
전 괜찮습니다
You may be OK... but I know
this is not true for your mother.
당신이야 괜찮겠죠
하지만 당신의 어머니는
안그러실겁니다
We both know that
she is dying of the virus.
어머님이 바이러스로
죽어가고 계신걸 알잖아요
Unless she gets the right medication,
she'll soon be dead.
제대로 된 약이 없다면,
곧 돌아가실 겁니다
You know the problem
with buying medicine in this country
문제는 케냐에서
약을 사는게
is that you never know if what
you're buying is real... or counterfeit.
진짜 약인지 짝퉁 약인지
알수가 없다는겁니다.
The doctors assure me that these
will have an immediate impact
의사가 이거면 바로
어머님의 건강상태에
on your mother's health.
효과가 나타날거라고
장담했습니다
What do I have to do for them?
내가 뭘하면 되죠?
All you need to do is protect this bag
이 가방을
잘 간직하다가
and make sure it arrives
at this address by midnight tonight.
이 주소로 오늘 자정까지
배달만 하면 됩니다.
Should be a rather simple task
for a man of your abilities, no?
당신같은 능력자에겐
간단한 일 아닌가요?
What are you doing
hiding in the dark?
어둡게 해두고
뭐하고 있니?
Waiting for you.
아빠 기다렸죠
I know you've been avoiding me.
절 피하고
있다는거 알아요
Your outburst in front
of my assistant was childish.
내 비서 앞에서 분노를
보인건 어리석었다
I needed to get your attention.
아빠의 관심이
필요했거든요
I have been here every night,
난 매일 밤
이곳에 있었다
negotiating a very important deal
with the Americans.
미국인들과 중요한
거래를 협상중이였지
Put the cigarette out.
담배 꺼라
You know I hate it when you smoke.
담배피는거
싫어하는걸 알텐데
You're too late.
아빤 너무 늦었어요
The auditors already know.
회계 감사쪽에서
이미 알았어요
Someone in this company
has been deliberately devaluing
이 회사의 누군가가
의도적으로
certain pharmaceutical stock in order
to move funds from one account to another.
특정 제약주 가격을 낮춰서
자금을 옮긴 사실을요
This kind of transaction
happens every day.
이런식의 거래는
매일 일어나
That may be...
그럴지도..
but this kind of transaction
is called embezzlement.
하지만 이런 거래는
횡령이라고 불립니다
Someone is going to jail for it.
이 일로 누군가는
감옥에 가야돼요
And I think we both know who.
그리고 우리 둘다
누가 갈지 알죠
We want the most
expensive wine you have.
여기서 제일 비싼
와인으로 주세요
- Felix.
- We have an amazing Bordeaux.
- 펠릭스
- 아주 좋은 보르도 와인이 있습니다
Is it the most expensive?
그게 제일
비싼거에요?
- Yes, I believe it is.
- Then we'll take it.
- 네, 그렇습니다
- 그럼 그걸로 주세요
One time, just one night,
한번만,
딱 오늘밤만
I want to live like I'm one of them
Arab sheiks or Russian billionaires.
아랍 왕자나 러시아
억만장자처럼 해보고 싶어
Tonight, I don't want to be
just Felix Bernner.
오늘밤은 펠릭스 베너가
아니고 싶어
Tonight, I say, no fucking limits!
오늘밤은 제한없이
놀아보자!
Hey.
야
You all right?
괜찮은거지?
Yeah, sure.
그래, 당연하지
I know what you're going through, Nomi.
노미씨, 무슨일을 겪는지 알아요
In just the span of a single day,
겨우 단 하루만에
you can see how much more damage
the disease has done.
이 병이 얼마나 더 손상을
입혔는지 보일겁니다
The tissue has nearly completely
merged the hemispheres.
이 조직이 거의 대뇌반구와
합쳐진게 보이실거에요
I'm sure the hallucinations
are getting more and more intense.
환각이 점점 더 자주보이고
선명하게 보일겁니다
And I have a feeling that you know
who started that fire.
그리고 제 생각엔 누가 병원에
불을 질렀는지 알것 같아요
I don't know anything about that.
전 아무것도
몰라요
Whoever they are, they aren't helping you.
그게 누구든, 당신을
도와주는게 아니에요
I don't know what they taught you
in med school, but the word "helping"
도대체 의대에서 뭘 배웠는지 몰라도
"도와준다"라는 단어는
doesn't mean handcuff people
and chop up their brains.
사람 묶어놓고 뇌를
잘라낸다는 뜻은 아니거든요
Michael!
마이클!
Nurse, I was gonna operate
tomorrow morning,
간호사, 내일 아침에
수술하려고했는데
but I don't think Ms. Marks here
can afford to wait.
하지만 여기 마크스양께선
기다리실수 없다네요
No, no, no, no.
No, I'm fine. I can wait.
아뇨,아뇨,아뇨,아뇨
아니에요, 전 괜찮아요, 기다릴게요
Cancel my rounds. Prep her for surgery.
제 회진 취소하세요.
이 분 수술준비해요
Yes, doctor.
네, 의사선생님
Sorry, lady, this is a private club.
죄송합니다,숙녀분
여긴 프라이빗 클럽입니다
I don't want to cause a scene.
I know this is a sex club.
소란피우지말지
여기 섹스 클럽인거 다 알아
No chicks but naked chicks.
벗은년은 들어가도
그냥 여잔 못들어가
My brother's in there
and I need him to come with me.
내 남동생이 안에 있고,
내가 데려가야한다고
Ain't gonna happen.
그럴수는 없을거다
Fuck off.
꺼져
Hey, you OK?
헤이, 괜찮아?
You can wait here, Officer Gorski.
여기서 기다려,
고르스키 경관
I'll go get Lieutenant Duncan.
내가 던칸
부서장님 불러올게
Whoo!
Come with me.
같이 나가자
It's OK.
This is my big sister, everyone.
괜찮아
모두들, 이쪽은 우리 누나야
- Hi.
- Hi, sister.
- 안녕하세요
- 안녕하세요, 누님
She doesn't mean
to make an ass out of herself.
누나가 일부러 싸가지 없게
보이려는건 아닌데
She just can't seem to help it.
근데 그냥 싸가지가 없네요
Father needs to talk to you.
아빠가 너 찾으셔
Are you fucking kidding?
지금 장난해?
- I'll see him tomorrow.
- No. He's waiting.
- 내일 뵈면 돼
- 안돼, 지금 기다리고 계셔
- In the middle of something important--
- Joong-Ki!
- 난 지금 중요한 일 중이니까...
- 중기야!
Now.
당장
Will! So good to see you.
윌! 만나서 정말 반가워
Did you have to wait long?
오래 기다렸어?
No, no. It's good to see you.
나투 오랭마니에욤
I didn't know you spoke Korean.
너가 한국말 하는줄 몰랐는데?
(나도 저게 한국말인줄 몰랐는데?!)
What?
뭐요?
You honor us with your presence.
와죠소 용광이네 #$#@과네는
Though your wife
is a cock sucking whore.
조가튼 쌍뇨니지만
Hapkido. Black belt.
합기도. 검은띠
Thirteen years. My sensei had
the foulest mouth in the entire Midwest.
13년 했지, 나의 사부는 미중서부에서
가장 더러운입으로 유명했지
- How's your dad?
- He's doin' good.
- 아버진 어떠셔?
- 잘지내셔요
I haven't seen him
since the retirement party.
은퇴 파티이후로
한번도 못뵈었네
I don't think I've ever seen
so many shitfaced cops
그때만큼 많은 경찰들이
꽐라된 모습이랑
from so many precincts in one bar.
그만큼 여러 관할서에서 온 경찰들이
모인 술집을 본적이 없다네
Your dad was a legend.
너희 아버지는
전설이셨어
Is. Is a legend. Sorry, Will.
아직도 전설이시지..
미안해, 윌
So, uh, what can I do you for?
그래서, 어, 무슨일이야?
Uh, it's about that perp I brought in,
Jonas Maliki.
어, 제가 검거한 범인
조나스 밀라키때문에요
What about him?
그 사람은 왜?
Was just hoping I could ask him
a few questions.
그냥 몇가지 좀
물을 수 있을까해서요
Ah, sorry, Will, no can do.
아, 미안하네, 윌
불가능해
It's federal.
You know how those guys are.
FBI 소관이야,
걔네가 어떤지 잘알잖아
We're only holdin' him here
until he's transferred.
우린 그냥 이송전에
맡아둘뿐이야
You should've called first.
It would've saved you a trip.
그냥 전화로 물었으면,
여기까지 안와도 됐을텐데
All I need is five minutes with him.
Family friend here.
전 딱 5분이면 되요,
가족같은 친구잖아요
This is a personal favor.
개인적인 부탁이에요
This look like a place
that gives a shit about personal favors?
여기가 지금 개인적인 부탁을
들어줄수있는곳 같니?
I'm sorry, Will, but rules are rules.
미안해, 윌
그런데 규칙은 규칙이야
Give my best to your dad.
아버지께 안부전해드려라
I'll send Greg to take you out.
내가 그렉보고
너 데려다주라고 할게
Damn it!
이런 젠장!
Will.
윌
You're here.
여기 있네요
- I can feel you.
- Yes, you can.
- 당신을 느낄 수 있어요
- 그래, 느낄 수 있어
But you're not really here, are you?
그런데 여기에 진짜로
있는건 아니죠, 그쵸?
No.
그래
I'm in solitary confinement.
난 지금 독방에
감금되어있어
Angel called it "visiting."
안젤은 이걸
"방문"이라고 불렀어
Members of a cluster do it instinctively
and others, like us, outside the cluster,
무리의 구성원들은 본능적으로 할 수 있어
그리고 무리 외의 사람들인 다른사람들과는
can visit if they've made visual contact,
eye-to-eye.
너랑 나처럼 눈과 눈끼리 시각적인
접촉을 한 후에 방문이 가능해져
This is cold.
이거 차갑네요
How can I feel this unless I'm here?
제가 여기 없는데
이걸 어떻게 느끼는거죠?
Because I feel it.
왜냐면 내가
느끼는거거든
No, this doesn't make sense.
아뇨, 이건 말도 안돼요
- You just spoke Korean, Will.
- I can't speak Korean.
- 넌 아까 한국말도 했잖아
- 전 한국말 못해요
Yes, you can,
and when you get it, you will.
아니, 넌 가능해
그리고 너가 이해하면, 가능해져
Get what?
뭘 이해하면요?
You are no longer just you.
너가 더이상
너 혼자가 아니란걸
Mr. Gorski?
Will you come with me, please?
고르스키씨?
그럼 같이 가실까요?
OK.
오케이
It was so dramatic, Dad.
진짜 너무
극적이였어요, 아빠
Sun made an absolute spectacle of herself.
누나가 쪽팔리게
했다니까요
- Really embarrassed me and--
- Shut the hell up!
- 진짜 저도 창피해서..
- 닥쳐, 이자식아
Do you have no idea what you have done?
너가 뭔짓을
했는지 알아?
What are you talking about?
무슨 말이세요?
Do you think I am so stupid
넌 애비가 멍청해보였냐
that I don't know when
someone is stealing from me?
누가 내 돈을 훔쳐
가는지도 모를정도로?
Stealing from my clients?!
내 고객의 돈에
손을 대?!
Tomorrow the authorities are going
to come here and confiscate our records.
내일 검찰에서 나와서
우릴 압수수색할거다
And your face,
the face of our company...
그리고 니놈의 쌍판때기와
우리 회사의 간판이
will be in every newspaper,
on every news program,
모든 신문지와
뉴스에 도배가 될거다
and everything I have built
over the past 40 years will be gone.
그리고 내가 지난 40년간
쌓아올린게 전부 사라지는거지
Do you understand?
알아들었니?
알아쳐먹었냐고?
They are going to arrest you.
널 체포할거다
Oh, my God.
오, 마이 갓
You taught me how to bend the rules.
아빠가 법을 구부리는
방법을 가르쳤잖아요
Bend them, not break them.
법을 구부리랬지,
법을 깨버리라했냐
This isn't all my fault!
다 내 책임은
아니에요
Other people were involved.
It's not just me.
다른 사람들도 연관되있어요,
저만 그런게 아니라고요
Please, Dad, I can't go to prison.
제발, 아빠
저 감옥가기 싫어요
I'll do anything.
뭐든지 할게요
Even now...
you don't know how to act like a man.
지금까지도...
넌 남자같이 구는법을 몰라
What do you want me to do?
Kill myself?
그럼 어쩌길 바라세요?
자살할까요?
I want you to think of someone
other than yourself.
너 자신만 생각하지말고
다른 사람도 생각하라는거다
For you, this is impossible,
and it's my fault.
근데 너는, 그게 불가능하지
이건 다 내 잘못이다
I spoiled you.
내가 널 망쳤다
I raised you, and I failed.
내가 널 키웠고,
내가 널 실패했다
My wife, God rest her beautiful soul,
내 아내는, 하나님 제 아내의 영혼을 굽어주소서...
raised the one child
이 재앙을 벗어날
유일한 방법을 알고있는
capable of seeing the only way
out of this disaster.
한 아이를 키워냈지
What?
뭐라고요?
Did you say a way out?
방금 벗어날
방법이라고요?
Sun. Sun has a way out?
선, 누나한테 벗어날
방법이 있다고요?
Because Father rarely even admits
he has a daughter...
아빠는 딸이 있다는걸
좀처럼 인정안하셨고
because no one knows who I am
or what I do at this company,
아무도 내가 누군지도 모르고
내가 이 회사에서 뭘하는지도 모르니
if I confess to your crime,
만약 내가 너의 범죄를
뒤집어쓰고 자백하면
the company may be able
to survive the scandal.
회사는 스캔들로부터
벗어날 수 있다 이런거겠지
Oh, my God.
오, 마이 갓
Sun... you can save us?
누나...우리 좀 살려주면 안돼?
Please, Sun.
제발, 누나
Please save me. Please, Sun.
제발 나좀 살려줘,
제발, 누나야
Please, save me. Please.
제발, 살려주라, 제발
Jonas?
조나스?
- Will.
- The fuck?
- 윌
- 슈발?
We don't have much time.
시간이 없어
I tried to contact you.
당신한테 연락하려고 했어요
Visiting is not calling
or texting someone.
방문은 전화나
문자하는게 아냐
It's not something you make happen.
It is something you let happen.
그건 뭔가 해내는게 아니라
그냥 뭔가 생기게 냅두는거야
It took me quite some time
to understand the difference.
나도 그 차이를 이해하는데
많은 시간이 들었어
I'm hoping it won't take you as long.
너가 이걸 빨리
이해하길 바란다
You also have to learn the difference
between "visiting" and "sharing."
넌 또 "방문"과 "공유"의
차이점도 알아야돼
Visiting is what we're doing now.
방문은 지금 우리가
하고 있는거고
Sharing is something
you can only do inside your cluster,
공유는 오직
무리원들끼리만 가능한거야
accessing each other's knowledge,
language, skill--
서로의 지식, 언어, 기술을 공유하는거지
- What's a cluster?
- You have seven other selves now,
- 도대체 무리가 뭐에요?
- 너는 이제 7개의 다른 너 자신이 있는거란다
but unless you hurry,
there's only going to be six.
지금 서두르지 않으면,
이젠 6개로 줄어든다
One of you is about to be destroyed.
하나가 곧 파괴되기
직전이거든
I told you when we first met,
her name is Nomi Marks.
내가 첫만남에 이야기했지,
이름은 노미 마크스
She lives in San Francisco.
그녀는 샌프란시스코에 살아
You have to save her, Will,
너가 구해야 돼, 윌
and in so doing, save yourself.
그리고 그렇게 하는게
곧 너를 살리는거지
Wait, wait! Jonas!
기다려, 잠시만!
조나스!
Jonas.
조나스
OK, this is it.
오케이, 시간됐다
Doctor's getting ready.
의사선생님이
준비하고 계셔
No.
안돼요
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
자,자,자,자,자,자
- Don't, please. Please.
- It's OK.
- 이러지마요 제발, 제발
- 괜찮아요
- Relax. We're not gonna hurt you.
- Please, please, no.
- 진정해요. 해치는게 아니에요
- 제발, 제발 안돼요
- No, no, no.
- You are OK.
- 안돼요, 안돼요
- 괜찮아요
Please don't do this. Please.
제발 이러지마요 제발
Please don't. Please don't. Please!
제발 이러지마요,
제발 하지마요 제발요!
- Please!
- Hey, hey, hey, hey.
- 제발
- 헤이,헤이
No.
안돼요
- It's OK, it's OK.
- OK.
- 괜찮아요, 괜찮아요
- 됐어요
No. You're murdering me.
안돼요,
지금 절 죽이는거라고요
Don't say that.
We are helping you.
그런말 말아요
우린 돕는거니까
- It's for your own good, believe me.
- No.
- 당신을 위한거에요, 내말 믿어요
- 안돼요
Oh, God! Oh, God, somebody help me.
오, 하나님! 오,하나님
누가 좀 살려주세요
- Somebody help me!
- Who are you?
- 누가 저 좀 살려주세요!
- 누구에요?
Help me.
도와줘요
Fuck!
씨발!
I remember... what it felt like
to be loved by her.
기억이 나는구나...
너의 엄마에게서 사랑받은 기억이
It was a long time ago...
아주 오래전이였지...
but I still remember that feeling.
하지만 아직도 그
느낌을 기억한단다
Now we both know...
how it feels to lose it.
그리고 이제 우리 둘다
잃은 아픔이 어떤지 알지
Riley, it's Dad.
라일리, 아빠다
God, I hope you get this.
제발 이 메세지가 전해지길
I wanted you to be the first to know.
너가 제일 먼저
알았으면 좋겠구나
Riles, they want me back
with the symphony.
라일스, 교향단에서 내가
복귀하길 원하는구나
Said they couldn't imagine
playing Beethoven without me.
나 없이 베토벤을 연주하는건
상상이 안간다더구나
I know it's hard for you
to come home, but...
너가 집으로 돌아오는게
힘들다는걸 알지만...
Well, you know how much I love you
and what it would mean to me
하지만 내가 널 얼마나 사랑하는지
그리고 내가 널
to look out past the lights and know
you were there, you were listening.
빛 너머로 연주를 듣고 있는걸
본다는게 나에게 어떤의미인지 알길바란다
OK. I hope you're OK.
그래,잘지내렴.그래
Love you, Dad.
사랑한다, 아빠가
Ooh! Oh, Shugs!
오! 오! 셕스
Oh, tell me you love me!
Tell me you love me! Aah!
오, 사랑한다고 말해!
사랑한다고 말해줘! 아!
Shh! Shh!
쉬! 쉿!
- Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah! Oh, yeah!
- Fuck...
- Shh!
- Yeah! Aah!
- Yeah! Oh, I fucking love you, Shugs.
- Shh!
- 예! 존나 사랑해, 셕스
- 쉿
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh!
- Come on, Shugsie.
- I fucking am!
- 빨리, 셕시.
- 박고있다고!
Oh, come on, Shugsie!
더빠르게, 셕시!
Come on! Yeah! Oh, yeah.
Yeah! Oh, yeah.
I'm gonna fucking come,
I'm gonna come.
아 시팔 쌀것같아
아 쌀것 같아
- No, not yet, not yet! Not yet!
- I'm gonna fucking come!
- 안돼, 아직, 아직, 안돼
- 아 쌀거 같아!
- Come on!
- One song!
- 빨리!
- 한곡만!
- I'm too drunk.
- One song. I know you want to!
- 너무 취했어
- 한곡만. 너도 부르고 싶잖아!
Too drunk is why karaoke was born!
카라오케는 많이
취했을때 하는거라고!
Come on, get up!
어서, 나가!
Yeah!
예에!
Hey, hey, hey!
야,야,야!
Wolfgang.
볼프강
Fuck you!
엿먹어!
엿 먹 어!
Yeah! Yeah!
그렇지! 그래!
나 중기야. 우리 이야기좀 할까?
옛날처럼. 사랑해 누나!
Ah, come on.
아, 제발
Oh, my gosh! I love this song!
오, 어쩜!
나 이노래 완전 좋아해!
Hey, hey!
헤,헤이!
Wolfie!
울피!
노래 : Whats Up - 4 Non Blondes
♪ 내 나이 25살에 아직도
♪ 험난한 희망의
언덕을 오르려 해요
♪ 한가지 목적을 위해서
♪ 내 삶의 의미를 고민하는
순간 깨달았어요
♪ 세상이 인류애로
이루어졌다는것을
♪ 그게 무슨 의미가
있는지 모르지만
♪ 가끔 침대에 누워
눈물을 흘려요
♪ 내 머리 속에 있는 것을
모두 떨쳐버리기 위해
♪ 그러면 난 약간 이상한
느낌이 들어요
♪ 그리고 난 노력합니다
오 하나님, 난 노력합니다
♪ 나는 항상 노력합니다
이런 제도에서
♪ 그리고 나는 기도하죠
♪ 오, 하나님, 난 기도해요
♪ 나는 매일같이 기도해요
♪ 혁명을 위해서
♪ 그리고 난 말하죠, 이봐요
세상이 어떻게 되가는 거예요?
♪ 그래서 난 아침에 일어나
밖으로 나와서 심호흡을 하죠
♪ 그러면 기분이 좋아져요
♪ 그리고 목청껏 외치죠
세상이 어떻게 되어가는 거예요?
♪ 그리고 난 말하죠, 이봐요
세상이 어떻게 되가는 거예요?
Kala?
칼라?
You were singing in English and dancing.
너 영어로 노래부르면서
춤추고 있었어
I was dreaming.
나 꿈꾸고 있었어
You were smiling at someone.
누굴 보면서
미소짓는거 같던데?
Oh, dear.
오, 이런
I have never seen you smile like that.
너가 그렇게
미소짓는거 처음봤어
OK, was it Rajan?
그래, 그거 라진이였지?
Come on. Come on.
제발 어서
Oh...
오오...
What just happened?
뭔일이 있던거야?
Dr. Metzger is freaking out.
Let me know when you find out anything.
메츠거 의사가 완전 놀랬어요
뭐라도 알아내면 알려주세요
Sure.
네
Excuse me, Miss?
Do you need help, Miss?
저기요, 아가씨
도움이 필요하신가요, 아가씨?
Excuse me! Officers!
저기요! 경비님들!
She's mine. I've got her.
괜찮아요, 제 환자에요
Ms. Keene, I told you
I'd take you outside.
킨양, 제가 말했죠
데리고 나가겠다고요
I gotcha. I gotcha.
괜찮아 괜찮아
OK. OK.
오케이, 오케이
OK, could use a little bit of luck here.
그래, 여긴 조금 운이
좋아야할것 같다
OK.
좋아
Excuse me. Hey.
Hey! Hey, you two!
실례합니다,저기요
헤이,헤이 거기 두명
Sorry! I'm sorry! I'm sorry.
We really need this now. I'm sorry.
미안해요! 미안해요! 미안해요!
저희가 먼저 탈게요, 미안해요
Sorry, thank you.
미안해요, 고마워요
Castro, please!
캐스트로로 가주세요!
Oh, God!
오, 갓!
- Oh!
- OK, OK.
- 오!
- 괜찮아, 괜찮아
Thank you.
고마워
Thank you, thank you, thank you.
고마워, 고마워, 고마워
It's OK. I love you.
괜찮아, 사랑해
I love you.
사랑해
Come on. I gotcha.
이리와, 내가 여깄어
I gotcha. Come on, you're safe.
내가 여깄어,
괜찮아. 넌 안전해
You're safe. OK? OK.
이제 안전해,
알았지? 알았지?
- Oh. Oh, I said "Hey."
- What, sweetie, what?
- 그리고 난 말하죠, 이봐요
- 뭐라고? 자기야? 뭐?
Uh... I've had this song
stuck in my-- my head all day.
어....한 노래가 있는데
하루종일 머리서 떠나질 않아
- "I said 'Hey, hey.' I said 'Hey.'"
- 4 Non Blondes.
- "그리고 난 말하죠, 이봐요, 이봐요"
- 4 Non Blondes
That's a perfect soundtrack
for a lobotomy.
뇌수술하기에
아주 완벽한 노래지
Mm.
What's going on?
세상이 어떻게 되가는 거예요?
세상이 어떻게 되가는거야?
한글자막제작 by 홍자막
hongej89@naver.com
Sync and corrected by Elderfel
www.addic7ed.com